# **NAKUL MALIK**

DIGITAL MARKETING

## DETAILS

#### PHONE

+91 880-071-4091

### EMAIL

nakulmalik.184@gmail.com

## LINKS

Linkedin

My YouTube Channel

## SKILLS

Digital Marketing

Google Adwords

Social Media Management

Email Marketing

SEO Copywriting

Content Creation

Google Analytics

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Create Memes

## LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

## HOBBIES

Create Meme Listen to Music Mov&Chill

### PROFILE

Hi! I am Nakul Malik, A Digital Marketer having 2+ years of experience in different fields of Digital Marketing as it is a broad umbrella term. From Social Media Marketing (SMM) to Search Engine Marketing (SEM). or From increasing website traffic (organic/paid) to Social media reach (organic/paid). I also know a little bit of Photoshop (3.8 Star), Illustrator (2.5 Star), Wondershare Filmore (3.5 Star). For entertainment, I also work on my YouTube Channel "Bass Roasters" and also makes MEMEs (4 Star).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY	
<b>Digital Marketing Executive, Shalitin Immigration</b> Sep 2020 — Present	Delhi
<b>Digital Marketing Executive, APPPL Combine</b> May 2019 — Jul 2020	Delhi
SEO Executive, MCM Infotech Nov 2017 — Nov 2018	Delhi
INTERNSHIPS	
Digital Marketing, Aptech Malviya Nagar Jul 2017 — Oct 2017	Delhi
EDUCATION	
B.A. Prog, University of Delhi	Delhi
12th Delhi Police Public School	Delhi

12th, Delhi Police Public School Delhi

10th, Delhi Police Public School Delhi

## COURSES

## ACWD Pro, Aptech Malviya Nagar

## SEO SKILLS

- · SEO Tools Google Keyword Planner, Google Search Console, Google Analytics, etc.
- · SEO Process On-page, Off-page
- · Ads Formation Create ads using Google Adword, and also have a knowledge of creating ads on the social media platform like Facebook, Instagram, etc.

